The Ocean,
vast and innumerably large,
The Internet is at its core
A Sea of Data
Especially when you start to look
at the scale of it all...
In the age of Algorithms,
Our scope of the internet is skewed
We rely on finding specific things,
else, we go to our usual places
India, as an example,
has shown their people
tend to have common spots
they tend to search
In some circles,
it's joked upon that people
dare to touch the second page of Google.
But that begs the question,
How many resources it may provide?
Using various topics, it can link to over
10 pages of information
Assuming your algorithm is
filtered to your taste.
Perhaps it could lead to
more if unfiltered
These numbers, in a way, are comparable
to fish.
The amount we see on a daily basis may not
be a whole lot
And then you see a school of fish, a swarm
that can potentially range to having
hundreds, if not thousands, of
fish found in the wild.
Or even ants, a species known to
outnumber the human population
by a significant number
On a standard basis, its not a whole lot.
You're not gonna see fish daily
You're not gonna see a
swarm of ants daily.
But that puts into perspective
how much we don't see.
To further extenuate this, there are
potentially 2 billion websites
across the globe. While it is estimated
the remaining active websites are
somewhere in the two millions, which is
still staggering.
Some may be for casual use
Some for Businesses, Artistic Intent, or
to explain concepts to others
On the internet, there is nearly
limitless potential